[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "In which fictional town does the show take place?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Houston",
      "Hanford",
      "Hamilton",
      "Hawkins"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Hawkins"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the name of the four friends favourite fantasy tabletop game?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "The 13th Age",
      "Quests Of Yore",
      "Dungeons & Dragons",
      "Shadowrun",
      "Star Wars Roleplaying"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Dungeons & Dragons"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Who were the creators of the hit TV show?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "The Samsung twins",
      "The Duffer brothers",
      "Bernard Manning",
      "Quentin Tarantino",
      "Steven Martin"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Duffer brothers"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What was Kaliâ€™s number at the Hawkins Lab?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "002",
      "007",
      "012",
      "008"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "008"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the alternate dimension in Stranger Things named?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Mangletown",
      "Demogorgon",
      "The Upside Down",
      "Mind Flayer",
      "Sunnyside Up"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The Upside Down"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Who is the first person from Hawkins Hgh School to die at the hands of The Demogorgon?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Barbara Windsor",
      "Barcardi B",
      "Barbara Holland",
      "Bambi Stevens",
      "Barb Banners"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Barbara Holland"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which character from the show is British, and was born and raised in Spain?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Jim Hooper",
      "Eleven",
      "Max Mayfield",
      "Bill Byers",
      "Steve Harrington"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Eleven"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "How many times was the show rejected by several networks before starting filming?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "15-20",
      "20-40",
      "1-5",
      "5-15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15-20"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Who does vampire impresion on Haloween in Hawkins?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Bob Newby",
      "Steve Harrington",
      "Lucas Sinclair",
      "Eddie Munson"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Bob Newby"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which character admits they are scared of horror movies?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Eddie Munson",
      "Max Mayfield",
      "Eleven",
      "Murray Murray Bauman",
      "Karen Wheeler"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Max Mayfield"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What famous horror movie character player 'Victor Kreel' in Season 4 of Stranger things?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Hannibel Lecter",
      "Freddy Krueger",
      "Michael Myers",
      "Leatherface",
      "Chucky"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Freddy Krueger"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "1077",
      "1150",
      "1089",
      "1126",
      "1244",
      "1999"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1077
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "In 'Hell is Other Robots' Bender turns to which religion to help overcome his addiction?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "League of Sciencology",
      "Temple of Robotology",
      "Church of Roboism",
      "Order of Mechanology"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Temple of Robotology"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a member of the Ultimate Robot Fighting League?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "The Clearcutter",
      "Millionaire Bot",
      "Sergeant Feces Processor",
      "The Chain Smoker",
      "The Gender Bender"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Millionaire Bot"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "In 'The Cryonic Woman' what was the name of the leader of the feral adolescents that challenges Fry at Deathrolling?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Butch",
      "Zed",
      "Spike",
      "Snake"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Zed"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What rank does Kif hold in the DOOP?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Sergeant",
      "Captain",
      "Lieutenant",
      "Major"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Lieutenant"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Who are the two recurring cops, often seen around New New York?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Jonesy and ISP",
      "Smitty and URL",
      "Brady and Dotcom",
      "Harry and Capslock"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Brady and Dotcom"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "In 'Insane in the Mainframe', who is Fry's room mate at the Asylum for Criminally Insane Robots before Roberto is moved in?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Joey Mousepad",
      "Tinny Tim",
      "Hedonismbot",
      "Malfunctioning Eddie"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Malfunctioning Eddie"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which product successfully uses a dream advert to market itself to Fry?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Slurm",
      "Bachelor Chowm",
      "Lightspeed Briefs",
      "Mom's Robot Oil"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Lightspeed Briefs"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What was Fry's job in 1999?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Pizza Delivery Boy",
      "Newspaper Delivery Boy",
      "Milkman",
      "Shoe Shine Boy",
      "Postman"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Pizza Delivery Boy"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What company does Dr. Farnsworth run?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Space Express",
      "FexEd",
      "Earth Express",
      "Planet Express",
      "Federal Express"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Planet Express"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Futurama was amlost called what?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Doomsville or Aloha Mars",
      "Lrrrenconcilable Ndndifferences",
      "Futurella",
      "World of Tomorrow"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Doomsville or Aloha Mars"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What are the pest animals in New New York?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Rats",
      "Mutated Gators",
      "Owls",
      "Pigeons",
      "Omicrons"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Owls"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "In Love's Labours In Space which club did Leela visit to find a partner?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Club Extravaganza",
      "Bubble Bar",
      "Hip Joint",
      "O'Gorgnaxs"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Hip Joint"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "In Fear of Bot Planet what fake religious robot holiday did Bender make up?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Bot-Mitvah",
      "Robanza",
      "Robonukah",
      "Robotisam"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Robonukah"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "In Fry and the Slurm Factory what did Fry and Bender use to look in the Slurm cans?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "X-Ray",
      "Z-Ray",
      "Lookamatic 5000",
      "F-Ray"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Lookamatic 5000"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What was the name of Fry's dog?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Buster",
      "I.C. Wiener",
      "Robo-Dog",
      "Seymour Asses"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Seymour Asses"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What is Planet Express's Slogan?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Our crew is replaceable. Your package isn't",
      "Good news everyone",
      "We are the fastest service, no matter how long it takes.",
      "We will get it there, eventually.",
      "If it ain't broke, we'll break it."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Our crew is replaceable. Your package isn't"
  }
]
